Guide to the Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records, 1936-ongoing UA.09.05.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accessions UA 93-137, UA 93-140, and UA 94-44, 1969-1993, 3 boxes
  UA 94-44 (1978-1987): minutes, brochures, financial records, correspondence, memoranda, reports, handbooks, and other materials.
  Arranged as received, in accession number order, then alphabetically within each accession; accession numbers are recorded on the folders.
  - UA 93-137, 1969-1991
    - Affiliate Artist Program, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
    - Afro-American Corridor, 1969-1972 (Box 18)
    - Association of Independent Houses (AIH), 1975-1983 (Box 18)
    - AIH--judicial board, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
    - Architect Selection Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
    - ASDU--Ad Hoc Committee on residential life, 1979 (Box 18)
    - CCA Committees, 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Central Campus Housing Facility, 1975-1985, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Dean Howard Strobel, 1975-1981 (Box 18)
    - Energy Management Advisory Council, 1980-1984 (Box 18)
    - Energy Rebate Program, 1981-1984, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Experimental Education Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
    - Few Lounge, 1983-1991 (Box 19)
    - Fraternity Freshman Experiment, 1969-1976 (Box 19)
    - Graduate Center, 1969-1976 (Box 19)
    - Housing director--Larry Smith, 1973-1977 (Box 19)
    - "J-Buddy" Program, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Judicial Review Committee, 1977-1988 (Box 19)
    - Learning/ Living Program--experimental, 1981-1990, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Reaccredation Self-Study, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - Residential Committee, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Residential Governance Study Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 19)
    - Residence hall--proposed, 1981-1985, 5 folders (Box 19)
      Folder 4 contains blueprints.
    - Self-Pacing Program, 1982 (Box 19)
    - Self-Study report, 1977 (Box 19)
    - STP Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Student Affairs--staff meetings, 1988-1991 (Box 19)
    - Student Emergency Loan Fund (Douthat Cox), 1961-1978 (Box 19)
    - Users Committee (New Residence Hall), 1983-1985 (Box 19)
    - Women's Center task force, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
    - Year-Round Operation study, 1980 (Box 19)
  - UA 93-140, 1982-1993
    - Accounting manual, 1990-1992 (Box 19)
    - Accounting manual for treasurers of student organizations, 1988-1990 (Box 19)
    - A Development Wish List, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Clubs and organizations, 1984 (Box 19)
    - East Campus Enhancement Committee, 1987-1991, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Ethnic-inclusive student internship program, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Faculty Associates (of student groups), 1982-1983 (Box 19)
    - Multiculturalism task force, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
    - Parties/ spaces, etc., 1984-1986 (Box 19)
    - Student Activities--a presentation to the Student Affairs Trustee Committee, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Student Activities--brochures and mission statement, 1989-1993 (Box 19)
    - Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program (SALAP), 1986-1987 (Box 19)
    - Student Activities newsletter, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
    - Technological innovation and the division of student affairs at Duke University, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Undergraduate Publications Board Handbook, 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - UA 94-44, 1979-1986
    - Sports clubs, 1979-1983 (Box 20)
    - Sports Club Council, 1980-1986 (Box 20)
    - Sports Club Council--budget files, 1981-1983 (Box 20)
    - Sports Club Council--correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 20)
    - Sports Club Council--minutes, 1980-1986 (Box 20)
- Accession UA 94-102, 1980-1992, 1 boxes
  Correspondence, memoranda, printed mater, financial records, and other materials concerning Parents' Weekend (1975-1991), reprographics services, the automation of the office, and the professional activities of the staff in national student services associations.
  - American College Personnel Association(A.C.P.A), 1984-1989 (Box 20)
  - ASDU--club subsidies, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - ASDU--SOC, 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Bookkeeping course--atendence, 1981-1985 (Box 20)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (NASPA), 1983-1989 (Box 20)
  - National Conference on Student Services (N.C.S.S.), 1986-1988 (Box 20)
  - Parents' Weekend, 1980-1991, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Placement computerized bidding and bid system, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Reprographics services, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs Computer Center, 1983-1992 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs Computer Center--consultant applications, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs Computer Center--general information, 1986-1990 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs Computer Education/Consulting Center (S.A.C.E.C.C.)--Local Area Networking Seminar, 1989 (Box 20)
- Accession, unnumbered, 1979-1993, 2 boxes
  Miscellaneous files from various student groups, arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Alumni correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 20)
  - Archive--correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 20)
  - ASDU--correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 20)
  - ASDU--miscellaneous and unrecognized clubs, 1979-1989 (Box 20)
  - Audits, 1986-1988 (Box 20)
  - Audits--Auditor's Daily Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 20)
  - Financial Forms Workshop, undated (Box 20)
  - Insurance Bonding on Student Business Managers, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Master copies, 1986-1990 (Box 21)
  - S.A.L.A.P., 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - S.A.L.A.P.--workshops, 1985-1987 (Box 21)
  - Student Activites--accounting manuals and brochures, 1979-1993, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Student Activites--contingency account, 1982-1988 (Box 21)
  - Student Activities file, 1985-1993 (Box 21)
  - Student Activities and Off-Campus Accounts--financial records, 1986-1989 (Box 21)
  - Workshops and workshop proposals, 1987-1990 (Box 21)
- Accession UA 97-85, 1972-1995, 3 boxes
  Case files on student organizations, including the ASDU, campus publications, fraternities and sororities, and cultural, geographical and other interest groups. The records include lists of officers, charters and other material.
  - Access, 1987-1989 (Box 21)
  - ACE (Association of Collegiate Entrepreneurs), 1987-1992 (Box 21)
  - The Alpha and Omega Bible Study, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
  - Alpha Delta Pi, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi, 1988-1991 (Box 21)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi Fraternity, 1988-1991 (Box 21)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Alpha Pi Alpha--charter file, 1980-1991 (Box 21)
  - Alspaugh House, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Alpha Tau Omega, 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Anthropology Majors Union--budget, charter, and corespondence files, 1977-1984 (Box 21)
  - The Archive--charter file, 1967-1991 (Box 21)
  - Art Majors Union, 1981-1989 (Box 21)
  - ASDU, 1977-1992, 21 folders
    - Bail Loan Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 21)
    - Charters, 1987-1990 (Box 21)
    - Check cashing, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
    - Check Cashing Report, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
    - Contingency Fund, 1982-1984 (Box 21)
    - Depreciation and insurance, 1989 (Box 21)
    - Legislature, 1977-1991, 4 folders (Box 21)
    - Maternity-Abortion Student Loan Fund, 1988 (Box 21)
    - Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
    - Newsletter, 1980-1982 (Box 21)
    - Non-recognized organizations, Parents' Weekend, President's Discretionary Fund, and projects, 1984-1989 (Box 21)
    - Proposals, 1980-1983 (Box 21)
    - Recognition request, 1991-1992 (Box 21)
    - Recognized clubs/organizations, 1989-1991 (Box 21)
    - Student Organization Commission (S.O.C.), 1982-1992 (Box 21)
    - SOC allocations, 1987-1992, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - SOC subsidies, 1989-1991 (Box 21)
  - Association for Student/Faculty Interaction1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Association for Troop Support, 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Bike Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 21)
  - Black Graduate and Professional Student Council, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - Black Student Weekend Planning Committee, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Blue Devil Underwater Discovery, 1987-1989 (Box 22)
  - Bravo Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 22)
  - Bridge Club, 1981-1990 (Box 22)
  - BSA--Black History Month, 1980-1985 (Box 22)
  - BSA/Black Student Newspaper--Prometheus Black, 1979-1992 (Box 22)
  - BSA--programming, 1981-1990 (Box 22)
  - Cable T.V., 1980-1988 (Box 22)
  - Chi Epsilon, 1985-1990 (Box 22)
  - The Chinese Club, 1986-1989 (Box 22)
  - Chinese Scholars' Friendship Association, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - Chi Omega, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
  - Chorale, 1983-1990 (Box 22)
  - The Chronicle--Publication Board, 1985-1990 (Box 22)
  - Civil Liberties Union, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Class of '89-'93, 1987-1992 (Box 22)
  - Community Services Network, 1986-1991 (Box 22)
  - Conference on Career Choices, 1980-1990 (Box 22)
  - Constitution and Purpose, 1981-1983 (Box 22)
  - Council of Class Presidents, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Council on Human Relations, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Cultural Groups, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Davison Society, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Debate Team--correspondence, 1974-1990 (Box 22)
  - Delta Gamma Fraternity, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1985-1989 (Box 22)
  - Delta Sigma Phi, 1984-1989 (Box 22)
  - Delta Sigma Theta--correspondence, 1982-1990 (Box 22)
  - Delta Tau Delta, 1980-1985 (Box 22)
  - The Devilettes (Duke University Twirling Ensemble)--charter file, 1982 (Box 22)
  - Divinity School Student Association, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Drama Students Union, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke Acquaintance Rape Program, 1987-1989 (Box 22)
  - Duke Aviators Club, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Duke Bar Association, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke Beatrician Society, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - The Duke Blue, 1986-1991 (Box 22)
  - Duke Career Network, 1981-1986 (Box 22)
  - Duke Coalition for Peace in the Mid-East, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Duke Companions, 1982-1991 (Box 22)
  - Duke Dancing Devils, 1986-1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke Engineer, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke Green Guide, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke Homeless Project, 1986-1989 (Box 22)
  - Duke Humanities Review, 1980-1987 (Box 22)
  - Duke Investment Club, 1983-1989 (Box 22)
  - Duke Jazz Society--correspondence file, 1984-1987 (Box 22)
  - Duke Journal of Argumentation and Debate, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke Journal of Politics, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
  - Duke Parliamentarians, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Duke Recycles, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke South and Southern Africa Coalition, 1985-1989 (Box 22)
  - Duke Students for America, 1983-1988 (Box 22)
  - Duke Students for the Brady Bunch, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke STUDY (Students Teaming Up with Durham Youth), 1990-1992 (Box 22)
  - Duke Toastmaster's, 1989-1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke University Black Pre-Health Organization, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Duke University Classics Society, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Duke University Experimental Living/Learning Program, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Duke Women's Handbook, 1987-1990 (Box 22)
  - Duke Youth in Crisis, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Economics Majors Union, 1978-1982 (Box 22)
  - Engineering Socity Community Outreach Projects, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Epsilon Sigma Alpha--Kappa Psi, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Eta Kappa Nu, 1982-1990 (Box 22)
  - Exam Pack, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Forem Club, 1990 (Box 22)
  - French Club, 1985-1990 (Box 22)
  - Friends of African Youth, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Geology Club--charter file, 1976-1991 (Box 22)
  - Giles Dorm, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Graduate and Professional Women's Network, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Hanes--Annex and House Council, 1987-1988 (Box 22)
  - Hats Off!, 1984-1989 (Box 22)
  - History Majors Union, 1985-1990 (Box 22)
  - House Y-W and House Z, 1987-1989 (Box 22)
  - Humor Extravaganza, 1984-1986 (Box 22)
  - IEEE (Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers), 1985-1991 (Box 22)
  - International Affairs Forum, 1985-1990 (Box 22)
  - Interns in Conscience, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Italian Club--correspondence, 1985-1992 (Box 22)
  - Jabberwocky, 1982-1989 (Box 22)
  - Kappa Alpha Order, 1985-1989 (Box 22)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1983-1995 (Box 22)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    [Restricted until 2020.]
  - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1985-1990 (Box 22)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
  - Kappa Sigma, 1984-1994 (Box 22)
  - Karamu--Black Students Alliance, 1977-1995 (Box 22)
  - Lancaster Language House, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Latent Image, 1985-1992 (Box 22)
  - Libertarians, 1983-1989 (Box 22)
  - Linking Individuals with Nonprofit Charities (LINC), 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - Marine Lab Club, 1985-1989 (Box 22)
  - Mary Lou Williams Center--budget, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Men Acting for Change, undated (Box 22)
  - Missing Link, 1983-1992 (Box 22)
  - Model Congress, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Music Association--correspondence file, 1981-1990 (Box 22)
  - National Association of Black Students for Educational Pursuits (NABSEA), 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - North Carolina Public Interest Research Group (NCPIRG)--charter file, 1972-1987 (Box 23)
  - NROTC Commodore Club, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Omega Phi Psi--concert file, 1974-1986 (Box 23)
  - Omicron Delta Epsilon, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1982-1984 (Box 23)
  - Order of St. Patrick, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Peer Information Services for Counseling and Education on Sexuality (PISCES)--charter file, 1977-1993 (Box 23)
  - Penny Productions, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Phi Delta Theta--correspondence file, 1971-1985 (Box 23)
  - Phi Kappa Phi--correspondence, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Phi Kappa Psi--correspondence, 1971-1982 (Box 23)
  - Pi Beta Phi, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Pi Tau Sigma, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Political Science Majors' Union--correspondence file, 1983-1989 (Box 23)
  - President's Honor Council, 1984-1989 (Box 23)
  - Project Outreach, 1989-1991 (Box 23)
  - Project Share, 1989-1992 (Box 23)
  - Project Share, Duke University, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Psychology Majors' Union--charter file, 1976-1991 (Box 23)
  - Purgatory, 1992 (Box 23)
  - PUSH (People Understanding the Severely Handicapped), 1985-1991 (Box 23)
  - Radio Board, 1980-1992 (Box 23)
  - Rape Prevention Education Project, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Recycling Cooperative, 1989-1991 (Box 23)
  - Reginaldo R. Howard Memorial Organization, 1972-1989 (Box 23)
  - Register Illinois, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Religious Life Finance Council, 1988 (Box 23)
  - The Round Table, 1990-1992 (Box 23)
  - SASC (Study Abroad Student Committee), 1987-1990 (Box 23)
  - The Sceptic, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Senior Leadership Awards, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Shoot Out for Literacy, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon--Cheating in College Athletics Symposium and correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 23)
  - Sigma Chi, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Sigma Nu, 1984-1992 (Box 23)
  - Society of Black Engineers, 1979-1991 (Box 23)
  - SOC By-Laws, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Social Dance Club, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Spanish-American Latin Student Association (SALSA), 1980-1991 (Box 23)
  - Starfleet: USS Dominion, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Students Against World Hunger, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - Student/Alumni Relations Committee, 1981-1990 (Box 23)
  - Student Faculty Service Project, 1988-1990 (Box 23)
  - Students for a Democratic Central America (SDCA), 1984-1988 (Box 23)
  - Students for Al Gore, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Students for Fiscal Responsibility, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Students for Gantt, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Students for Helms, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Students for the Exploration and Development of Space, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Students for the Program in Film/Video, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Students for the Protection of Privacy and Individual Freedom, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Students Guide to Duke, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Student travel services, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Symphony Orchestra, 1981-1995 (Box 23)
  - Symposium Committee, 1982-1992 (Box 23)
  - Symposium for Confronting Rape Culture Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 23)
  - Tau Beta Pi, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Teacher-Course Evaluation Book--correspondence file, 1974-1990 (Box 23)
  - The Texas Club, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Transfer Advisory Council (TAC), 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - W. G. Pearson Science Explorers, 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - The Women's Coalition, 1982-1989 (Box 23)
  - The Writer's Circle, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha, 1988-1990 (Box 23)
- Accession UA 2005-0038, 1963-2005, 3 boxes
  Office of Student Activities and Facilities records include subject files relating to the Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival (1983), Major Speakers, the Undergraduate Publications Board, Freewater grants, the Kammerer Award, the Blackburn Literary Festival, and adviser training.
  - The Archive, 1997-2003 (Box 23)
    [Restricted until 2028.]
  - Blackburn Literary Festival, 1997-2004, 3 folders (Box 23)
    [Restricted until 2029.]
  - Chanticleer, 1992-2001, 2 folders (Box 23)
    [Restricted until 2026.]
  - Corman Project--Conquered New Horizans, 1999-2000 (Box 23)
    [Restricted until 2025.]
  - Duke Student Publishing Company, Inc. (DSPC)--correspondence, 1998 (Box 23)
    [Restricted until 2023.]
  - Duke Yearlook, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Eruditio, 1996-2003 (Box 23)
  - Film and Video at Duke, 1979-1986 (Box 23)
  - Freewater Productions, 1963-2004, Folder 1-2 of 16 (Box 23)
    Grant applications, proposals, requests, and contracts; approved grants; and history of Freewater.
  - Freewater Productions, 1963-2004, Folder 3-16 of 16 (Box 24)
  - Grüv Productions, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
  - Kammerer Award / Prize, 1983-2004, 20 folders (Box 24)
    Documentation of the history of the "Hal Kammerer Memorial Award for Original Student Film or Video Production, Duke University." The files contain the annual nominees and winners of the award from 1985-2004, including the filmmakers' descriptions of their films. The first folder in the group documents the establishment and early history of the award, circa 1983-1984, "to recognize outstanding achievement in the art and science of film or video production." [Note: entitled both "award" and "prize" in various years.]
  - Latent Image, 1996-1997 (Box 24)
    [Restricted until 2022.]
  - Lecture Bureau information, 1994-1995 (Box 24)
  - Major Speakers, 1992-2004, 9 folders (Box 24)
    Margarethe Commermeyer, Ed Meese, John Waters, Simon Wiesenthal, Douglas Wilder, Barry Williams, Presidential candidates, and previous years' problems.
  - Mary Biddle Duke Foundation--Paul Fleschner (Freewater Productions), 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, 1982-1983 (Box 25)
  - OSAF meeting agendas and supplemental information, 2004-2005 (Box 25)
    [Restricted until 2030.]
  - Prometheus Black, 1997-2001 (Box 25)
  - Publication Board, 1963-2003, 24 folders
    - Administration-advisor minutes, 1999-2002 (Box 25)
      [Restricted until 2027.]
    - Advertising Prospectus, 1997-1998 (Box 25)
    - Bassett Fund, 1963-2002 (Box 25)
    - Blind Spot, 1999-2000 (Box 25)
    - Board, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
    - Budget, 1993-2003, 4 folders (Box 25)
    - Business manager, 1980-1997 (Box 25)
    - Carpe Noctem, 1999-2002 (Box 25)
    - Computer information, 1999-2001 (Box 25)
    - Constitution, 1981-1995 (Box 25)
    - Copyright information, undated (Box 25)
    - Craft Center and Publication Board Cooperative Agreement, 1999-2000 (Box 25)
    - Distribution, 1986-1992 (Box 25)
    - Editors, 2002 (Box 25)
    - History, 1969-1996 (Box 25)
      [Restricted until 2021.]
    - Inter-Community Council (ICC) By-Law, 1995-2002 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-2002 (Box 25)
    - Open Forum, 1996-2000 (Box 25)
    - Parents' Weekend Wine and Cheese Reception, 1997-2002 (Box 25)
    - Pending, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
    - Printing bids, 1997 (Box 25)
  - Salty Observer, 1997 (Box 25)
  - Small Programs Committee, 2003-2005 (Box 25)
  - Suspended publications, 1994-1996 (Box 25)
  - Teacher-Course Evaluation, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Tobacco Road, 1997; A 3.5" floppy disk image; approximately 2 megabytes.
    Conditions Governing Access
    [Electronic records in this file have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.]
  - Tobacco Road, 1999-2001 (Box 25)
  - Vertices, 2000 (Box 25)
  - Women's Handbook, 1997 (Box 25)
  - Young America's Foundation, 2003 (Box 25)
- Accession UA 2005-0068, circa 1970-2003, 150 folders
  Office of Student Activities and Facilities records include subject files relating to: (Box 1) visual arts exhibits, gallery spaces, gallery security systems, Last Day of Classes, Broadway at Duke, the Experience Music Project, and (Box 2) additional Broadway at Duke. Materials range in date from circa 1970-2003; the bulk of the materials date from 1999-2003. 2000 items, 3.0 lin. ft.
  - Broadway at Duke (BAD), 1969-2004, 38 folders (Box 25)
    - Budget, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
    - Donors and donor parking, 1999-2002 (Box 25)
    - History, 1981-2001 (Box 25)
    - Playbill ads, 2001-2003 (Box 25)
    - Playbill, 1999 (Box 25)
      [Restricted until 2024.]
    - Subscriber brochures and order forms, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
    - Ticket orders, 1969-1970 (Box 25)
    - Adaptation/Next brochure and final box office reports, 1970-1971 (Box 25)
    - Annie Get Your Gun, 2001 (Box 25)
    - Cabaret, 2001-2002 (Box 25)
    - Chicago, 1998-2001 (Box 25)
    - The Complete Millennium Musical--Reduced Shakespeare Company, 1998-2000 (Box 25)
    - Darrow, 1998-1999 (Box 25)
    - Fame, 2002-2003 (Box 25)
    - Footloose, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
    - Forbidden Broadway, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
    - Fosse, 2000-2002 (Box 25)
    - Hadrian VII, 1970-1971 (Box 26)
    - Kiss Me Kate, 2000-2004 (Box 26)
    - John Leguizamo, 2003-2004 (Box 26)
    - Little Women--the Musical, 2000-2003 (Box 26)
    - Patti Lupone, 2000-2001 (Box 26)
    - Master Class, 1995-1999 (Box 26)
      contains electronic media
    - National Shakespeare Company, 1999-2000 (Box 26)
    - Ragtime, 2000-2001 (Box 26)
    - Rent, 2001-2003 (Box 26)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 2003 (Box 26)
    - Saturday Night Fever, 2003 (Box 26)
    - The Scarlet Pimpernel, 2002 (Box 26)
    - Smokey Joe's Café, 1999-2000 (Box 26)
    - South Pacific, 2002-2003 (Box 26)
    - Les Tambours du Bronx, 1999-2001 (Box 26)
    - 1776, 1970 (Box 26)
    - Tom Selleck in A Thousand Clowns, 2000-2001 (Box 26)
    - Titanic, 2001-2002 (Box 26)
    - To Be Young, Gifted, and Black, 1969-1971 (Box 26)
    - Victor/ Victoria, 1999 (Box 26)
    - Zorba, 1970 (Box 26)
    - BAD digital materials, 1998-2002; 3 3.5" floppy disk images; approximately 9 megabytes.
      [Restricted until 2027]
      Scope and Contents
      The documents include subscriber brochures, subscriber order forms, committee notes, and tour programs.
  - Visual Arts Committee, 1975-2000, 25 folders
    - Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 26)
    - Notes, 1975-2000, 4 folders (Box 26)
    - Paintings sold, 1992-1995 (Box 26)
    - Sentry Watch, Inc., 1995 (Box 26)
    - Studio surveys, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Visual Studies workshop, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Brown Gallery, 1995-1998, Folders 1-6 of 13 (Box 26)
      Files on the following exhibits in the Bryan Center's Louise Jones Brown Gallery: Mary Crutchfield, 1997; Andre Leon Gray, 1998; Jacqueline Hammer, 1995-1997; Holly Hanessian and Crystal Crawley, 1998; Patricia Kordas, 1996-1997; Vera Knight, 1996.
    - Brown Gallery, 1995-1998, Folders 7-13 of 13 (Box 27)
      Files on the following exhibits in the Bryan Center's Louise Jones Brown Gallery: Tina Marcus, 1996; Paul Nabatoff, 1996; Aemilia Papaphilippou, 1997; Charles E. Rawlings, 1998; Jonathan Sharlin, 1995; Joani Spadaro, 1996-1997; and Gail Henderson Weinerth, 1996.
    - Chalk for the Earth (Chalk Art on the Walkway), 1996 (Box 27)
    - Lilly Library Gallery; Mark Dolejs, 1997; and Jacob Colley, 1995-1997, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Various files--events, Duke Union, and Major Attractions, 1970-2005, 18 folders
    - Committee on the Performing Arts (CPA), 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - DSG--annual budgets and miscellaneous, 2002-2005 (Box 27)
    - DUU Performing Arts--box office reports and correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 27)
    - DUU Performing Arts--Preservation Hall Jazz Band, 1970-1971 (Box 27)